Let X be some arbitrary set and suppose towards a contradiction that there is
a 1-1 and onto map f from X to the power set of X.
Where onto just means that every element in the power set
of X gets mapped to by some element from X.
We can define the diagonal set D as the subset of X consisting
of the elements which are not contained in their image under f.
This is a subset of X, and therefore
by definition exists somewhere in the power set.
By our assumption that the map is onto, there should
be some element a in X, such that f(a)=D.
By definition of D, we know that a in D iff a not in f(a).
But D=f(a), so we get that a in f(a)
iff a not in f(a), which is a contradiction.
So, it must be that our map was not onto, and therefore the size
of the power set of D is larger than the size of D.